Shortest job first
Mr face that
Vishal is having Delhi bus time we are going to schedule with Phosphorus cycle shortest
First
Ok to variation is preemptive and other one is non preemptive
And coming to this this one
Amazing
Which job is chosen it will not stop
Interior finishes
It is for non preemptive
Hindi Prem tourist visa which is also called as
Shortest
Vishal seat capacity theatre
Patna Vishal confirm our self study
Prem Ke bhashan
What does it means
Whenever you choose any process you are going to do anything completion otherwise you are not going to stop
How to how to do this
1st year
First I am going to use
Big and short
Arrival time is minimum is not there for no process I should ever 880
21 so
The first person which will be available will be at time one therefore from zero to one
Time one leave only for seven days EP 1
I am going to take P1 and run it in computer and it is non preemptive version right
How much time does it take for me to complete 7 minutes 21788
So now the time is it
By the time
Pratishat always remember this
You are trying to view next one you see that
Pick the next available for Salesforce scheduling
128 is over there four pic one Sunday available
Which one is which one is the best one
Kamal this paneer P3
Cp1 is over
Dekho Delhi Terminal T3 which is having the best time of one paper and take fees in next
Bus time of wonderful is going to be running till 9
Now
P3 is over then what is the next one with the least bus stand
Wishes to
Jaipur
Which is having a bus time of to there for the completion time is 11
Hello everyone is to another is 5
I have two forces
134 134 have 2 and 5
These two which one is having the least bus time
We want it
Delhi bus time is it
I am go to take P2
And we whose bus time is 5 then 4 11 + 56
Nokia 3 only one is remaining and it is already available at 16
FIFA which is it
416 + 8 is how much
Shortest shortest job first
Germany job
The question might be
Give any random combination of process with random
Possible arrival time
Our shortest job
Will always scheduling shortest job first
It is false
Study schedule on the available for psus the shortest job first which means that you are looking outstanding
Time one at this point of time one
Only for special level C1
That is not used but it doesn't mean that even is a shortage of right
Jaipur shortage of works in such a way that among available for certificate to take the shortest job
Guarantee that
Whatever you want I am always with you start with the list of first
Therefore in this case
It is 7
What happens in sometime
Heroine
Shortest job first will also fall fall victim to conversate Ameen
Not mention
The longest process between the process with the highest bus time watches bus time
Computer
Yes you are going for this one right there for shortest job first is also
Is it team of
Save this example
I think you understood this forget finish it off then I'll show you what is a problem with this is there
Shortest job first and then we can continue the next America
Write this page
What is the data structure which supports is algorithm
Got it
Among all the available processes
I might have to pick the
List one which means the one with the least bus time
For the min heap is suitable data structure for this
You can find the minimum
Delete delete delete it unit against basic advice
Tarzan
Maintain maintain the Bean property based on the bus stand
Deccan always root is going to the process with the
Nice bus time
And you are always going to remove it
Schedule
And so it out
What is the min heap is the best best data structure
This one
Every
One process will be added exactly once and exactly once
Therefore for every forces edition in one division
Condition is going to take login time adding element in the min heap
Admission is going to take login time right
Then into 2 interlocking therefore and login is the time complexity for this
Hi please refer to the algorithm in high point and come back and watch it
You didn't understand what I am saying you please go to algorithms what you can come back
Sexy about the complete and time
When did 1 complete
P1 completed at 8:00
And P2 completed 16
Petri completed at 9:00
P4 completed at 11:00
FIFA completed 24
After that we can find on the turnaround time
What is the timer on time
I told you that transfer on time is
Completion time - arrival time difference of these two
Then what is it
7 year
14 year
And it is 6 year
Editors
2nd year
And it is the
19 year
Is it on time
Xx
So what is waiting time I told you that waiting time is turnaround time - bus time
You can do all this very easily with this simple trick will think
I am doing it you can do it do it yourself
Not able to adjust
14 - 59
My son is 5
NDTV Lagan
Nothing like this
What is the average turnaround time and what is the average waiting time
So here also should be careful
That when you are standing at any point just see what are the process available don't directly go and pick up the Lost no
Bus stand
Also examples
This also
Manilal standard